A Guide to the Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 8, Accession 2018:011 FA1552
Rockefeller Archive Center
Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 8, Accession 2018:011
1969-2015
Rockefeller Archive Center
Henry Luce Foundation
FA1552
28.82 Cubic Feet 66 boxes, 65 letter-size document boxes, 1 half letter-size document box
Biographical / Historical
The Henry Luce Foundation was established by Henry R. Luce in 1936. As a New York-based nonprofit organization, the Luce Foundation awards grants in American Art, Asian studies, Higher Education, Theology, and supports the Clare Boothe Luce Program for women in science, mathematics, and engineering.
Scope and Contents
The Henry Luce Foundation records (Record Group 8) contains project files, publications, and some audio-visual material. The majority of project files are related to the American Art and Theology programs.
Arrangement
The Henry Luce Foundation records (Record Group 8) are arranged as follows:
Series 1: Project Files, 1983-2015
Series 2: Publications, 1969-2012
Series 3: Audio-Visual Material, 1992-2001
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
When requesting to view audiovisual material, please refer to the Title and the AV Number (example: AV 1916). Researchers are asked to check the "Restrictions" note for each Title. If a Title does not currently have an access copy, please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
All inquiries to view films require advanced notice of at least 2 business days, and may necessitate notice of up to one week. Individual items, including those that are not available in modern formats, may be restricted from access at the discretion of RAC.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by the Henry Luce Foundation in 2018.
Environmental aspects; Religions; International relations; Art, American; Research grants -- Asia, Southeastern; Education, Higher; Environmental sciences; Theology -- Scholarships, fellowships, etc.
- Project Files, 1983-2015; 1
  - Africa Network - Administrative Development and Pilot Programs, 2008-2014 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Akron Art Museum - National Tour of an Exhibition from the Whitney Museum of American Art, 2012-2014 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Alban Institute - Resources for Faith Leaders Facing Religious Realities, 2005-2013 (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
  - Albrecht-Kemper Museum of Art - Off-Site Programs and Technological Equipment (American Art Renewal Fund), 2010-2014 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Allentown Art Museum - Inventory the American Art Collection, 2012-2014 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - American Academy of Religion - Career Guide for Racial and Ethnic Minorities in Religious and Theological Studies, 2004-2013 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - American Academy of Religion - Religous Pluralism for Theological Educators Summer Seminars, 2008-2013 (Box 2, Folder 8-9)
  - American Center for Mongolian Studies - Fellow Program in Mongolia, 2008-2014 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - American Council on Education - At Home in the World: Educating for Global Connections and Local Commitments, 2010-2014 (Box 2, Folder 11-12)
  - American Society for Muslim Advancement - Development of a Global Muslim Women's Shura Council, 2007-2013 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - American Society for Muslim Advancement - Development of a Global Muslim Women's Shura Council (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - American Society for Muslim Advancement - Graduate Program in Islamic Law for Women, 2009-2013 (Box 3, Folder 14-15)
  - American Society for Muslim Advancement - Muftiyyah Training Program (MTP) Global Muslim Women's Shura Council, 2011-2013 (Box 3, Folder 16-17)
  - American Society for Muslim Advancement - Muslim Women Leaders Forum, 2006-2013 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - American University - Violence and Victims in Latin America: Churches and Religion in Dictatorship and Democracy, 2011-2014 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Americans for Oxford, Refugee Studies Center - Faith-Based Humanitarian Project, 2010-2014 (Box 4, Folder 20-21)
  - Andover Newton Theological School - Interreligious Leadership Training Program, 2008-2013 (Box 4, Folder 22-24, Box 5, Folder 25-27)
  - Andover Newton Theological School - Interreligious Leadership Training Program - Media Center Master: Circle Conversations V3, 2010 Interfaith (Box 4, Folder 22-24)
  - Anita Borg Institute for Women and Technology - Grace Hopper Celebration for Women in Computing Conference, 2008-2014 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Aquinas Institute of Theology - Professorship in Interreligious Theology, 2005-2013 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Arkansas Art Center - Curator of Drawings and Contemporary Craft Positions, 2011-2014 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Art and Religion in American Life, 1994-2001 (Box 6, Folder 31-34)
    Scope and Contents
    Proposal, meetings, project summaries, Crossroads, Twin Cities Project, Brooklyn Museum documentation, Monograph, book distribution.
  - Art Institute of Chicago - "John Marin's Watercolors: A Medium for Modernism" Exhibition and Catalog, 2009-2014 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Asian Cultural Council - American Artists and Museum Professionals in Asia Program, 2010-2014 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Asociacion para la Educacion Teologica Hispana (AETH) - Bible Institute Certification Standards, 2011-2013 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Asociacion para la Educacion Teologica Hispana (AETH) - Hispanic Theological Education Books and Manuals, 2008-2013 (Box 7, Folder 38-41)
  - Asociacion para la Educacion Teologica Hispana (AETH) - Renovacion: Renewing Latino Theological Education at the Grassroots, 2006-2013 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Association for Asian Studies - Annual Conference, 2013-2014 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Association of Art Museum Curators - Travel Grants for Junior American Art Curators to Attend the Annual Meeting, 2013-2014 (Box 7, Folder 44-46)
  - Association of American Colleges and Universities - General Education for a Global Century, 2010-2014 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Association of American Colleges and Universities - Models for International and General Undergraduate Education, 2005-2014 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Association of Theological Schools in the United States and Canada - Christian Hospitality and Pastoral Practices in a Multifaith Society, 2009-2013 (Box 8, Folder 49-50)
  - Association of Theological Schools in the United States and Canada - Christian Hospitality and Pastoral Practices in a Multifaith Society, 2012-2014 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Association of Theological Schools in the United States and Canada - Henry Luce III Fellows in Theology Program (2013), 2013-2014 (Box 9, Folder 52-53)
  - Association of Theological Schools in the United States and Canada - Henry Luce III Fellows in Theology Program (2012), 2012-2013 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Association of Theological Schools in the United States and Canada - Henry Luce III Fellows in Theology Program (2011), 2011-2013 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Association of Theological Schools in the United States and Canada - Henry Luce III Fellows in Theology Program (2010), 2010-2013 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Association of Theological Schools in the United States and Canada - Henry Luce III Fellows in Theology Program (2009), 2009-2013 (Box 9, Folder 57-58)
  - Association of Theological Schools in the United States and Canada - Henry Luce III Fellows in Theology Program (2008), 2008-2013 (Box 9, Folder 59-60)
  - Association of Theological Schools in the United States and Canada - Henry Luce III Fellows in Theology Program (2007), 2007-2013 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Association of Theological Schools in the United States and Canada - Henry Luce III Fellows in Theology Program (2006), 2006-2013 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Association of Theological Schools in the United States and Canada - Henry Luce III Fellows in Theology Program (2005), 2005-2013 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Association of Theological Schools in the United States and Canada - Henry Luce III Fellows in Theology Program (2001-2005), 2001-2013 (Box 10, Folder 64-65)
  - Association of Theological Schools in the United States and Canada - World Conference, Johannesburg, South Africa, 2011-2013 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Aspen Institute - Council of Women World Leaders Graduate Fellowship Program, 2009-2014 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Aspen Institute - International Issues and Congress, 2011-2014 (Box 11, Folder 68-69)
  - Auburn Theological Seminary - 10th Anniversary of 9/11 Public Education Campaign, 2011-2013 (Box 11, Folder 70-71)
  - Auburn Theological Seminary - Center for Multifaith Education (2010 Renewal), 2010-2013 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Auburn Theological Seminary - Center for Multifaith Education, 2008-2010 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - Auburn Theological Seminary - Center for Multifaith Education (2007 Renewal), 2007-2014 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Auburn Theological Seminary - Center for Multifaith Education, 2005-2014 (Box 12, Folder 75-76)
  - Auburn Theological Seminary - Center for Multifaith Education, 2003-2013 (Box 12, Folder 77-78)
  - Aurora University - "A Dictionary of Christian-Muslim Relations", 2007-2014 (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - Baylor University - Global Mission Leadership Initiative, 2008-2013 (Box 12, Folder 80, Box 13, Folder 81-82)
  - Baylor University - Global Mission Leadership Initiative - God-Called Mission-Driven, Global Mission Leadership Testimonies, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 80, Box 13, Folder 81-82)
  - Baylor University - Global Mission Leadership Initiative - Global Mission Leadership Scholars (Box 12, Folder 80, Box 13, Folder 81-82)
  - Baylor University - Global Mission Leadership Initiative, 2011-2013 (Box 13, Folder 83)
  - Baylor University - Global Mission Leadership Initiative, 2012-2015 (Box 13, Folder 84)
  - Bennington Museum - Building Maintenance (American Art Renewal Fund), 2011-2014 (Box 13, Folder 85)
  - Birmingham Museum of Art - American Art Curator and Exhibit Programs (American Art Renewal Fund), 2010-2013 (Box 13, Folder 86)
  - Blanton Museum of Art - "Converging Lines: Eva Hesse and Sol LeWitt" Exhibition and Catalog, 2013-2014 (Box 13, Folder 87)
  - Boston Athenaeum - "John Storrs: Architectural Forms" Exhibition and Catalog, 2009-2014 (Box 13, Folder 88)
  - Boston College - Lay Religious Program in the Institute of Religious Education and Pastoral Ministry (Renewal), 2007-2013 (Box 14, Folder 89-91)
  - Boston College - Total Community Catechesis, Institute of Religious Education and Pastoral Ministry, 2004-2013 (Box 14, Folder 92-94)
  - Boston University, School of Theology - Howard Thurman Papers Project, 2012-2014 (Box 14, Folder 95)
  - Brookgreen Gardens - Retrofit the Archives/Library Space (American Art Renewal Fund), 2011-2014 (Box 15, Folder 96)
  - Brooklyn Law School - "Religious Freedom and Equal Treatment: An International Look" Conference, 2013-2014 (Box 15, Folder 97)
  - Brooklyn Museum - American Art Activities (American Art Renewal Fund), 2011-2014 (Box 15, Folder 98)
  - Bureau for International Reporting - Religion and International Affairs, 2011-2014 (Box 15, Folder 99)
  - Butler Institute of Art - Folk Art Specialist, 2010-2014 (Box 15, Folder 100)
  - Butler Insitute of Art - Heating and Ventilation System (American Art Renewal Fund), 2010-2013 (Box 15, Folder 101)
  - Cambodian Association of Illinois - Cambodian Genocide Exhibition at the Cambodian American Heritage Museum and Killing Fields Memorial, 2009-2014 (Box 15, Folder 102)
  - Cambodian Association of Illinois - Cambodian Genocide Curriculum (Draft Copy) Created by NCPHS Students (Box 15, Folder 102)
  - Cambodian Association of Illinois - Silent Trauma: Diabetes, Health Status, and the Refugee - Southeast Asians in the United States - Appendices, Additional Reports on South East Asians and Diabetes, 2006 June (Box 15, Folder 102)
  - Candler School of Theology, Emory University - "Sharing Best Practices: Internationalizing Theological Education" Conference and Publication, 2009-2013 (Box 15, Folder 103)
  - Candler School of Theology, Emory University - Theological Education for Korean and Korean-American Students, 2004-2013 (Box 16, Folder 104-105)
  - Cape Ann Museum - Fitz H. Lane Collection, 2013-2014 (Box 16, Folder 106-107)
  - Carnegie Mellon University - Negotiation Skills Workshop for Women in Science and Engineering, 2012-2014 (Box 16, Folder 108)
  - Case Western Reserve University - Tibet Oral History and Archive Project, 2000-2014 (Box 16, Folder 109)
  - Case Western Reserve University - Tibet Oral History and Archive Project - TOHA Demo, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 109)
  - Case Western Reserve University - Tibet Oral History and Archive Project - Tibetan Oral History Demo 2 (Box 16, Folder 109)
  - Catholic University of America - "Erroneous Autonomy: The Catholic Case Against Libertarianism" Conference, 2014 (Box 16, Folder 110)
  - Cedar Rapids Musem of Art - Refurbish Permanent Collection (American Art Renewal Fund), 2010-2014 (Box 17, Folder 111)
  - Center for Independent Documentary - "Mysticism and Monotheism" Documentary Film, 2009-2013 (Box 17, Folder 112)
  - Center for Independent Documentary - "Mysticism and Monotheism" Documentary Film - Mysticism/Awakened Heart Excerpts (Box 17, Folder 112)
  - Center for Initiatives in Art and Culture - 19th Annual American Art Conference, 2013-2014 (Box 17, Folder 113)
  - Chicago Theological Seminary - Arts and Theology Initiative, 2006-2014 (Box 17, Folder 114-115)
  - Chicago Theological Seminary - Arts and Theology Initiative - Luce Foundation Report, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 114-115)
  - Claremont Graduate University - Institute for Signifying Scriptures, 2006-2013 (Box 17, Folder 116-117)
  - Cleveland Museum of Art - American Art Budget, 2011-2014 (Box 18, Folder 118)
  - Columbia Museum of Art - American Art Collection, 2009-2014 (Box 18, Folder 119)
  - Columbia University - Economic Incentives for Biodiversity Conservation, 2005-2014 (Box 18, Folder 120)
  - Columbus Museum of Art - Curatorial and Collections Assistant Positions (American Art Renewal Fund), 2011-2014 (Box 18, Folder 121)
  - Commonweal Foundation - Theological Writers Project, 2005-2013 (Box 18, Folder 122)
  - Commonweal Foundation - Theological Writing Project (Renewal), 2008-2013 (Box 18, Folder 123)
  - Connecticut Public Broadcasting - Study Guides on the Documentary "Asian and Abrahamic Religions: A Divine Encounter", 2010-2013 (Box 18, Folder 124)
  - Cornell University - Preservation Training Program for Chinese Academic Libraries, 2012-2014 (Box 18, Folder 125)
  - Council of Independent Colleges - 2010 Presidents Institute, 2009-2014 (Box 19, Folder 126)
  - Council for a Parliament of the World's Religions - Task Force on Interfaith Initiatives in Theological Education - Concluding Meeting, 2011-2013 (Box 19, Folder 127)
  - Council for a Parliament of the World's Religions - Participation in the 2009 Parliament in Melbourne, Australia, 2008-2013 (Box 19, Folder 128-129)
  - Council for a Parliament of the World's Religions - Operation and Program Costs, 2005-2013 (Box 19, Folder 130)
  - Currier Museum of Art - Assistant Curator and Librarian Positions (American Art Renewal Fund), 2010-2014 (Box 19, Folder 131)
  - Dominican University - Caritas et Veritas Symposium, 2010-2013 (Box 20, Folder 132)
  - Drew University Theological School - Drew Center for Christianities in Global Context, 2006-2013 (Box 20, Folder 133-134)
  - Drew University Theological School - Drew Center for Christianities in Global Context - CCGC Lecture: Chapel Service, Dr. Beauty Maenzanise, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 133-134)
  - Drew University Theological School - Drew Center for Christianities in Global Context - CCGC Lecture: Dr. Beauty Maenzanise, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 133-134)
  - East Asia Institute - Program to Strengthen Academic Links Between East Asia and the United States, 2004-2014 (Box 20, Folder 135-136)
  - East Asia Institute - Program to Strengthen Academic Links Between East Asia and the United States (Renewal), 2007-2014 (Box 21, Folder 137)
  - Elijah Interfaith Institute - Educational Program on Jewish Relations, Yeshiva Chovevei Torah, 2007-2013 (Box 21, Folder 138-139)
  - Emory University - Program on Law, Religion, and Human Rights, 2006-2014 (Box 21, Folder 140-141)
  - Faith and the City - Civic Engagement Program for Religious Leaders, 2007-2013 (Box 22, Folder 142)
  - Faith and the City - Leadership Institute, 2004-2013 (Box 22, Folder 143-144)
  - Faith in Public Life - Public Theological Leadership Program, 2006-2014 (Box 22, Folder 145-146)
  - Feminist Press - GPS to a Career in Science Program, 2011-2014 (Box 22, Folder 147)
  - Flaherty/International Film Seminars, Inc. - Exchange with China on Documentary Film, 2012-2014 (Box 22, Folder 148)
  - Foundation Center - Sustainable Arts in America, 2012-2014 (Box 23, Folder 149)
  - Franciscan School of Theology - Kenan Osborne Chair in Systematic Theology and Franciscan Intellectual Tradition Symposium, 2005-2013 (Box 23, Folder 150-151)
  - Fuller Theological Seminary - Evangelical Interfaith Dialogue, 2010-2013 (Box 23, Folder 152)
  - Fund for the City of New York/New York Faith and Justice - "Envision: The Gospel, Politics, and the Future" Conference, 2008-2013 (Box 23, Folder 153)
  - Fund for Reconciliation and Development - United States, Cambodia, Laos, and Vietnam, 2004-2014 (Box 23, Folder 154)
  - Fund for Theological Education - Recruitment of Candidates for the Christian Ministry, 2010-2013 (Box 23, Folder 155)
  - Fund for Theological Education - Recruitment of Candidates for the Christian Ministry, 2009-2013 (Box 24, Folder 156)
  - Fund for Theological Education - Recruitment of Candidates for the Christian Ministry, 2008-2013 (Box 24, Folder 157)
  - Fund for Theological Education - Recruitment of Candidates for the Christian Ministry, 2007-2013 (Box 24, Folder 158)
  - Fund for Theological Education - Recruitment of Candidates for the Christian Ministry, 2006-2013 (Box 24, Folder 159)
  - Garrett-Evangelical Theological Seminary - Professorship in Missions and World Religions, 2009-2013 (Box 24, Folder 160)
  - General Theological Seminary of the Episcopal Church - Center for Peace and Reconciliation, 2006-2014 (Box 25, Folder 161-162)
  - Georgetown University - Institute for Pastors on Islam and Christian-Muslim Relations, 2006-2013 (Box 25, Folder 163)
  - Georgetown University - Religion, Foreign Policy, and Global Development Program, 2006-2014 (Box 25, Folder 164-165)
  - Georgetown University - Berkeley Center's Project on Religion and Global Development, 2012-2014 (Box 25, Folder 166)
  - Georgia Museum of Art, University of Georgia - "Art Interrupted: Advancing American Art and the Politics of Cultural Diplomacy" Exhibition and Catalog, 2009-2014 (Box 25, Folder 167)
  - Give2Asia - China Development Brief, Beijing Civil Society Development Research Center, 2012-2014 (Box 26, Folder 168)
  - Glimpse Foundation - General Operating Support, 2006-2014 (Box 26, Folder 169)
  - Graduate Theological Union - Master of Arts in Islamic Studies, 2010-2013 (Box 26, Folder 170-171)
  - Florence Griswold Museum - Assistant Curator Position (American Art Renewal Fund), 2011-2014 (Box 26, Folder 172)
  - Hartford Seminary - Theological Educators Promoting Jewish, Christian, and Muslim Relationships, 2008-2013 (Box 26, Folder 173)
  - Hartford Seminary - Professorship in Jewish Studies, 2003-2013 (Box 27, Folder 174-176)
  - Hartford Seminary - Professorship in Jewish Studies, 2006-2013 (Box 27, Folder 177-178)
  - Hartford Seminary - Professorship in Jewish Studies - Introducing Hartford Seminary: A Place for Peace (Box 27, Folder 177-178)
  - Harvard Divinity School - Faculty Positions in Women's Studies in Ministry, 2006-2013 (Box 28, Folder 179-180)
  - Harvard Divinity School - Faculty Positions in Women's Studies in Ministry - Women in Ministry: A Panel Discussion, 2006 February 2 (Box 28, Folder 179-180)
  - Harvard University - "Natural Theology in Islam" Lecture, 2013-2014 (Box 28, Folder 181)
  - Harvard University - Teaching Pluralism: Case Studies for the Theological and Religious Studies Classroom, 2006-2013 (Box 28, Folder 182)
  - Harvard University - Religion and International Affairs: The Intersection of Policy and Scholarship Program, 2007-2014 (Box 28, Folder 183)
  - Harvard University Art Museums - Henry Luce Fund for the American Art Department, 2005-2014 (Box 28, Folder 184)
  - Hebrew College - Formation 2012 National Seminar, 2012-2014 (Box 29, Folder 185)
  - High Museum of Art - Part-time American Art Curator Assistant and Research Travel Funds for Two Years (American Art Renewal Fund), 2011-2014 (Box 29, Folder 186)
  - Hirschhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden - "Anne Truitt: Perception and Reflection" Exhibition and Catalog, 2007-2014 (Box 29, Folder 187)
  - Hirschhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden - Building Repairs, Temporary Curatorial Assistants, and Travel Funds (American Art Renewal Fund), 2011-2014 (Box 29, Folder 188)
  - Honolulu Museum of Art - "Art Deco Hawai'i" Exhibition and Catalog, 2013-2014 (Box 29, Folder 189)
  - Human Rights Watch - Religious Minorities in Indonesia and Pakistan, 2012-2014 (Box 29, Folder 190-191)
  - Huntington Museum of Art - Museum Debt (American Art Renewal Fund), 2011-2014 (Box 30, Folder 192)
  - In Trust - Presidential Search and Transition Process, 2011-2013 (Box 30, Folder 193)
  - Institute of Church Administration and Management - Strategic Planning, 2009-2013 (Box 30, Folder 194)
  - Institute of Church Administration and Management - Training for Leaders of Black Churches, 2005-2013 (Box 30, Folder 195)
  - Institute for Global Engagement - "African-American Religious Groups and U.S. Policy in the Middle East/North Africa," Review of Faith and International Affairs, 2008-2014 (Box 30, Folder 196)
  - Institute for International Education - Myanmar International Relations in Higher Education Initiative, 2013-2014 (Box 30, Folder 197)
  - Kalamazoo Institute of Arts - Completion of Permanent Collection Catalog, 2006-2014 (Box 30, Folder 198)
  - Kalamazoo Institute of Arts - Staff Position for the Permanent Collection (American Art Renewal Fund), 2010-2014 (Box 30, Folder 199)
  - Kindling Group - "The Calling" Documentary, 2009-2014 (Box 31, Folder 200)
  - Kindling Group - "The Calling" Documentary, 2008-2014 (Box 31, Folder 201)
  - Living Earth Television - Chinese Documentary Film, 2012-2014 (Box 31, Folder 202)
    China Inside Out, Horsemen, Colors of China, Choices
  - Lutheran School of Theology, Chicago - Center for Christian-Muslim Engagement, 2006-2013 (Box 31, Folder 203-204)
  - Lyman Allyn Art Museum - Curator and Boiler (American Art Renewal Fund), 2010-2014 (Box 31, Folder 205)
  - McCormick Theological Seminary - Center for the Study of Latino/a Theology and Ministry, 2006-2013 (Box 32, Folder 206)
  - Madison Square Park Conservancy - Mad. Sq. Art Program, 2013-2014 (Box 32, Folder 207)
  - Maine State Museum - "Uncommon Threads: Wabanaki Textiles, Clothing, and Costume" Exhibition and Catalog, 2008-2014 (Box 32, Folder 208)
  - Meadville Lombard Theological School - Integrated Community Model of Religious Formation, 2009-2013 (Box 32, Folder 209)
  - MentorNet - Academic Career E-Mentoring (ACE) Program, 2006-2014 (Box 32, Folder 210)